# MAAYANK GIRISH KOTHARI

KOTHARI MANSION 2,

ROOM NO 314, KJ SOMAIYA POLY. HOSTEL,

NEAR LAXMI TALKIES,

SOMAIYA VIDYAVIHAR CAMPUS,

SITABULDI, NAGPUR-440012.

VIDYAVIHAR(E), MUMBAI-400077.

Mob:- (+91) 8866753419

Email id:- maayank.k@somaiya.edu

#### **About ME**

Co-Founder of Campus Company branding CATALYST. I am always curious to learn new things. I love history and like to explore new things. I relish gaining experience in each and every field of life. An honest, good-hearted, adventurous person who loves to collect moments and not things.

## **Experience**

August 2017 – Present	October 2017 – Present	July 2017 – Present	
Co- Founder	Animation Team Member	Robotics Teacher	
Chief Technical Officer	Core Team Member	Volunteer	
branding CATALYST	KJSCE Outreach Centre	Ekagrata (NGO)	

#### **Education**

Graduation(UG)	12 <sup>TH</sup> Std.	10 <sup>th</sup> Std.	
2015 – 2019	2015	2013	
B.Tech Computer Science	Gujarat State Higher Secondary & Secondary Education Board		
CGPA:- 7.7/10 (Till Sem V)	83.38%	89.17%	
K J SOMAIYA COLLEGE OF ENGG, MUMBAI	SAINT XAVIERS' HIGH SCHOOL, ADIPUR(KUTC	H)	

## **Projects**

- Quiz Applet: A quiz app made using JAVA Applet.
- Students hostel portal: A website for hostel students. Tools used: HTML,CSS,PHP,AJAX,XML.
- Digi Dine (On Going): A web application for restaurant management.
- LocateME (On Going): An android app to locate nearby people using Proximity.
- D2D Communications (On Going): Technology that allows you to share your cellular network to the other device.

#### **Skills**

Non-Tech	Databases	Technical	Applications
Content Writing	Oracle 11G	Programming Language:	Microsoft Office Suite
Event Management	MS Access	C, Java	Word, Excel, Outlook
Languages known:	MySQL	Web Development:	PowerPoint, Project.
English, Hindi, Gujarati, Kutchi	PostGreSQL	HTML, CSS, PHP	Operating System use
Languages Learning:		Android Studios	Windows 98 & above
Spanish, Marathi		MATLAB, AUTOCAD	Ubuntu & Kali Linux

## **Certifications**

- 1) BASICS OF INCOME TAX (Completed)
- 2) An audit of ENTREPRENUERSHIP (Completed)
- 3) Hands on To Ethical Hacking (Present)
- 4) Interdisciplinary course on Cyber Security (Present)
- 5) An introduction to Psycology (Present)

#### References

References available upon request.

## **Additional Details**

- Events head for Athletics in SKREAM'18- a national level sports competition conducted by KJSCE
- Volunteer in "SWAACH" a cleanliness drive by IIT-Bombay in 2017 for Juhu Beach.
- Student Co-ordinator for program "ANCIENT WISDOM FOR MODERN SUCCESS" (2015-KJSCE)
- School Representative at "EXUBERANCE 2012: 20th AINACS meet" at St. Francis high school, Jamnagar (State Level)
- Qualified IIT-JEE (mains) 2015 (105/360)
- Gold medalist in school in International Maths Olympiad is(IMO) 2013

## **Interests**

- Sports: Football, Cricket, Badminton, Volleyball.
- Hobbies: Writing quotes, short stories, cooking and photography.
- I have a great passion for Travel & Tourism
- Love reading about history.